hamilton.edu 2019-12-07

# GDPR - Hamilton College

Hamilton College (“Hamilton”,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) is an institution of higher education. If  
you apply to Hamilton (as a student, employee, or faculty member), make online donations, view our webpage, use any of the systems or services Hamilton has contracted with, or complete any associated online forms, you should be aware that we will be collecting certain personal data from you.

As defined in the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”),  
“Personal Data” generally means any information that can be used to identify a natural  
person. If you are in the European Union, or if your Personal Data otherwise is subject to the  
GDPR, you should understand that we will use our technical infrastructure in the United  
States to deliver various services to you. In order to fulfill our contract with you (if you  
are an applicant, student, employee, or faculty member, or if you are purchasing items  
from us, browsing our website, etc.) we may need to transfer your Personal Data to the  
United States, and possibly to other jurisdictions outside of your home country, as  
necessary to provide these services. Similarly, if you are browsing our webpage, we  
may collect certain Personal Data about you (for example, your ISP address) in order to  
enhance our webpage, and your experience on our webpage, in accordance with our  
GDPR PRIVACY NOTICES below. Collection and processing of your Personal Data as you browse our webpage is necessary for our legitimate interests, and we believe these interests will not interfere with your fundamental rights or freedoms.
